# Svetlana Arkadyev

## Pharmacist - I&L Express Pharmacy

Huntingdon Valley, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Svetlana-Arkadyev/427fe2e64afc46bc

Highly trained Pharmacist with strong clinical abilities and a successful career in Hospital, Oncology ambulatory care and Retail facilities. Proactive and organized with passionate commitment to first-rate patient care. Licensed in PA with seven years of expertise.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

### **Pharmacist**

I&L Express Pharmacy - Philadelphia, PA - August 2014 to Present

Responsibilities:

Review prescriptions to assure accuracy, to ascertain the needed ingredients, and to evaluate their suitability. Provide information and advice regarding drug interactions, side effects, dosage, and proper medication storage.

Provide specialized services to help patients manage conditions such as diabetes, asthma, smoking cessation, or high blood pressure.

Collaborate with other health care professionals to plan, monitor, review, or evaluate the quality or effectiveness of drugs or drug regimens, providing advice on drug applications or characteristics.

Offer health promotion and prevention activities, for example, training patients on devices, such as blood pressure or diabetes monitors. Ensure compliance with all company procedures and federal and state laws, rules and regulations.

Perelman center for advanced medicine, Hospital of the University of Pennsylvania

### Clinical Oncology Pharmacist

Perelman Center for Advanced Medicine, Hospital of the University of Pennsylvania - Philadelphia, PA - October 2011 to June 2014

Reviewed physician orders and dispensing medications with a focus on research oncology protocol orders for ambulatory infusion service.

Reviewed patient specific parameters, doses, infusion time and concentrations for IV chemotherapy, monitored and helped manage drug therapies.

Worked with research protocols phase I-III for oral and IV medications

Followed preparation techniques and dispensing requirements.

Provided clinical information to healthcare providers, such as NP, MD, research and infusion

nurses, with regards to research protocols and standard therapies.

Was overseeing pharmacy technicians, interns and students and ensured accuracy of their work prior to dispensing.

On weekends worked in IV admixture room, providing medications for 900 beds hospital.

Prepared sterile solutions or infusions for use in surgical procedures, emergency rooms and general patient care.

## **Clinical Pharmacist**

Hospital of the University of Pennsylvania - Philadelphia, PA - February 2008 to October 2011

Collaborated with other health care professionals to plan, monitor, review, and evaluate the quality and effectiveness of drug regimens, providing advice on drug applications and characteristics.

Worked as clinical pharmacist in decentralized setting.

Followed patients on pharmacokinetics for antibiotic dosing.

Participated in discharge rounds.

Provided counseling for the patients.

Provided therapy recommendations to health care providers (Mds, NPs, PAs) regarding patient dosing based on patient specific parameters, such as CrCl and BSA based medications. •

Worked in IV admixture preparation room and supervised team of technicians.

Monitored and verified accuracy and preparation technics for various IV admixtures, including chemotherapy.

## Intern / Pharmacist

CVS Pharmacy - Langhorne, PA - September 2005 to February 2008

Communicated and interacted with physicians, nurses and dentists. •

Complied with all company procedures and federal and state laws, rules and regulations.

Was responsible for all aspects of Pharmacy Operations within the store, including inventory, personnel and customer relations.

### **EDUCATION**

## **PharmD**

Temple University School of Pharmacy May 2007

## **Associate in Critical Care**

Kiev Medical College - Kiev 1993